Speaker 1: Yes, brother.
Speaker 1: You had a question, yes.
Speaker 2: Well this uh booklet of Quran the ultimate miracle.
Speaker 2: I have with the cassette and the CNNcy.
Speaker 2: Um would you please uh
Speaker 1: Ah there was a book I had written, Al-Quran, the Ultimate Miracle.
Speaker 1: I had delivered talks on the subject and there were video tapes and cassettes available.
Speaker 1: But this man who originally made the discovery, which I found useful in talking to Muslims and non-Muslims.
Speaker 1: But this man, a sickness has developed, now he's claiming to be a new Rasulullah, like what Bahaullah was at one time, and Mirza Ghulam Ahmad.
Speaker 1: This is a sickness, this is a sickness that is quite common.
Speaker 1: You see, once a person, you know, he finds that he's so clever that people are, you know, hero-worshipping him.
Speaker 1: And you know, whatever I say, I know these people will believe.
Speaker 1: So the man creates a sickness, this man I can make claims. Today, this guy called Rashad Khalifa,
Speaker 1: he is the man who discovered this theory, Al-Ha-Thi-Sa-Ashar.
Speaker 1: Now he said he is the new Rasul. He's the messenger of God.
Speaker 1: There are certain flaws in the theory,
Speaker 1: but besides that now he's claiming now on the basis of that discovery that he is Rasulullah.
Speaker 1: And now he came out to proof first was that the Quran is Allah's Kalam, not changed, not one letter is changed.
Speaker 1: Now through the same theory is proving, he's trying to prove that look, the Quran is changed.
Speaker 1: That there are verses in the Quran which are not supposed to be there.
Speaker 1: Astaghfirullah.
Speaker 1: So I challenge this man to a debate.
Speaker 1: I send him a telegram that I'm prepared to hire the Madison Square Garden in New York at my expense.
Speaker 1: I said, 'You Khabiz from Tucson, come over.' And he says, 'I'll prove to the world that you are a kazzab, a liar, and a cheat, and a false.' False guy.
Speaker 1: So, he says, 'No, I don't want to come to the Medicine Square Garden. You come to Tucson in the private he wants to have a discussion.'
Speaker 1: That's a look.
Speaker 1: You're rubbish, there's no time for me to talk to people in private, come, come.
Speaker 1: You are the true messenger of God, then come forward, man, I'm prepared to talk to you.
Speaker 1: So, I have discontinued with the tape as well as the book and the cassette. No more.
Speaker 2: Well, you still endorsing that book that Quran the ultimate miracle?
Speaker 1: I've no more book, no more video, no more cassette, finish.
Speaker 1: There's so much more there, we don't want to create, you know, unnecessary strife among the Muslims and that guy every time I'm speaking he's trying to capitalize upon that.
Speaker 1: So he's trying to win your sympathy that he is a new messenger of God.
Speaker 1: Finish, we got nothing to do with him, he's an imposter and a liar and a cheat and a kazzab.
Speaker 1: Discontinued, finish, no more.